<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Morgrave Miscellany and Lingering Soul</title>
		<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-15153080/morgrave-miscellany-and-lingering-soul</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Morgrave Miscellany and Lingering Soul&quot; - Content from approved Homebrew Creators</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 20:21:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-15153080#post-5587123</guid>
				<title>Re: Morgrave Miscellany and Lingering Soul</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-15153080/morgrave-miscellany-and-lingering-soul#post-5587123</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 08:29:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>NCat</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6662241</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Links arent here yet, havent gotten to work on them, my bad. (Poor wording on the edit, I meant as in I added a bunch of stuff to the forum post)</p> <p>The links will be up once we properly get around to getting a start to them. Links will initially probably appear attached to this post, and then onto their respective class / home pages once fully ready</p> <p>Sorry for any confusion</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-15153080#post-5584442</guid>
				<title>Re: Morgrave Miscellany and Lingering Soul</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-15153080/morgrave-miscellany-and-lingering-soul#post-5584442</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 15:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>ThymeSaffron</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6941388</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Where can we find the links for all the things added for Morgrave? Will the subclasses be added to their respective class lists? I completely forgot Morgrave existed for a hot minute till I saw this, thanks for adding them!!!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-15153080#post-5565547</guid>
				<title>Morgrave Miscellany and Lingering Soul</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-15153080/morgrave-miscellany-and-lingering-soul#post-5565547</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 05:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>NCat</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6662241</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>While Im still sorta near completing the work for Exploring Ebberon homebrew races (Though my works been slowed due to a combination of my main computer kicking the bucket and being piled with exams), I've in the mean time happened to stumble upon two more lists of work by agreed upon homebrew authors:</p> <p><strong>Morgrave Miscellany - Keith Backer</strong><br /> This book is a supplement to Wayfinders Guide to Ebberon, and in terms of player resources, contains a number of subclasses, listed as follows:</p> <p>- Barbarian: Path of the Extreme Explorer<br /> - Bard: College of Keys<br /> - Cleric: Sovereign Domain<br /> - Druid: Circle of the Arbiter<br /> - Fighter: Bone Knight<br /> - Fighter: Vigilante<br /> - Monk: Argent Fist<br /> - Paladin: Oath of Sacrament<br /> - Ranger: Field Marshal<br /> - Rogue: Divine Herald<br /> - Sorcerer: Progenitor Spark<br /> - Warlock: Pact of the Host<br /> - Wizard: School of Antiquities</p> <p>I haven't yet gotten access to the book itself, but some of the archetypes from what I've been able to find have been pretty neat.</p> <p>Edit: Got access to a PDF, heres a few more things in it:</p> <p>Races / Subraces:<br /> - Halfling<br /> -<br /> -<br /> -<br /> - Shifter<br /> -<br /> -<br /> -<br /> - Tiefling<br /> - Dragonforged<br /> - Elf<br /> - Mark of Death<br /> - Child of Khyber<br /> - Abberent Elf<br /> - Abberant dwarf<br /> - Abbent Gnome<br /> - Abberant half elf<br /> - Abebrant Halfling<br /> - Abberant Half Orc<br /> - Abberant Human</p> <p>Dragonmark Feats:<br /> - Fledgling Mark of detection<br /> - Fledgling Mark of Finding<br /> - Fledgling Mark of Handling<br /> - Fledgling Mark of Healing<br /> - Fledgling Mark of Hospitality<br /> - Fledgling Mark of Making<br /> - Fledgling Mark of Passage<br /> - Fledgling Mark of Scribing<br /> - Fledgling Mark of Sentinel<br /> - Fledgling Mark of Shadow<br /> - Fledgling Mark of Storm<br /> - Fledgling Mark of Warding</p> <p>- Siberys Mark of detection<br /> - Siberys Mark of Finding<br /> - Siberys Mark of Handling<br /> - Siberys Mark of Healing<br /> - Siberys Mark of Hospitality<br /> - Siberys Mark of Making<br /> - Siberys Mark of Passage<br /> - Siberys Mark of Scribing<br /> - Siberys Mark of Sentinel<br /> - Siberys Mark of Shadow<br /> - Siberys Mark of Storm<br /> - Siberys Mark of Warding</p> <p>- Greater Abberant Dragonmark<br /> - Khyber Dragonmark</p> <p>- Fledgling Mark of Death (Feat)<br /> - Greater Mark of Death (Feat)<br /> - Siberys Mark of Death (Feat)</p> <p>Evolutionary Feats:<br /> - Atavist<br /> - Chameleon<br /> - Hierophant<br /> - Moonspeaker<br /> - Quori Nightmare<br /> - Spirit Rider<br /> - Warforged Collossus<br /> - Warforged Reclaimer<br /> - Weretouched Master</p> <p>Backgrounds:<br /> - Aspirant<br /> - Auditor<br /> - Cadet<br /> - Chronicler</p> <p><strong>Lingering Soul - Matthew Mercer</strong><br /> The lingeing soul is a class / alterante death rule that allows a player to play a ghost. Again, havent read the content absolutely fully yet, but I think the idea is quite neat, and I would think it could be cool on the wikidot. However, I do believe it should, if on there, have notes about &quot;Hey, you've gotta properly discuss this with a DM and all, this is homebrew and is also not designed for every game&quot;, because new players do use the site and etc. But aside from that, I think its pretty cool</p> <p>So yeah, thoughts on these sets of homebrew? I presume morgrave is a pretty straightforward include, though lingering soul im not sure? If we did include lingering soul, I think itd be better to have it in the homebrew section and not give it the bloodhunter treatment where it gets top of the page (which bloodhunter gets due to its overwhelming popularity and mainstream-ness).</p> <p>Yeah, just wanted to bring up things I found.</p> <p>Edit: Added a bunch of stuff from Morgrave</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>